A Guide to the Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning Heritage Resources Branch Slide Collection, 1967-1993
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning Heritage Resources Branch Slide Collection, 1967-1993
Fairfax County Public Library
2005.006
0.5 linear feet
The Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning Heritage Resources Branch Slide Collection consists of 940 slides depicting mostly historic Fairfax County structures spanning the years 1967-1993. Staff at the Fairfax County Heritage Resources Department photographed sites in Accotink, Alexandria, Annandale, Burke, Centreville, Chantilly, Clifton, Dranesville, Dulles, Fairfax, Fairfax Station, Falls Church, Floris, Fort Belvoir, Great Falls, Groveton, Gum Springs, Herndon, Idylwood, Langley, Lewinsville, Lorton, McLean, Mount Vernon, Newington, Reston, Seven Corners, Tysons Corner, and Vienna.
Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning Heritage Resources Branch staff
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
The Heritage Resources Branch transferred this slide collection to the Virginia Room in April 2005.
Historical and Biographical Information
In the early 1970s, at the urging of the Fairfax County History Commission, the Board of Supervisors hired professional staff to focus on preserving, researching, and documenting the county’s historical resources. Staff worked within the Division of Planning, which was later renamed the Office of Comprehensive Planning. In 1984, the county’s archaeological, historical and architectural resources staff were consolidated into the Heritage Resources Branch within the Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning. The County Executive dismantled the Heritage Resources Branch during the County Budget for FY 1996. The archaeology department staff transferred to the Fairfax County Park Authority; the historic buildings survey, architectural review, and historic district zoning staff were reassigned within the Office of Comprehensive Planning; and the historical research and publications program was completely eliminated. The changes took effect on July 1, 1996. As of 2019, the Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning is known as the Department of Planning and Zoning.
Scope and Content
The Fairfax County Office of Comprehensive Planning Heritage Resources Branch Slide Collection consists of 940 slides depicting mostly historic Fairfax County structures spanning the years 1967-1993. Staff at the Fairfax County Heritage Resources Department photographed sites in Accotink, Alexandria, Annandale, Burke, Centreville, Chantilly, Clifton, Dranesville, Dulles, Fairfax, Fairfax Station, Falls Church, Floris, Fort Belvoir, Great Falls, Groveton, Gum Springs, Herndon, Idylwood, Langley, Lewinsville, Lorton, McLean, Mount Vernon, Newington, Reston, Seven Corners, Tysons Corner, and Vienna. Some slides in this collection are duplicated slides which pre-date 1967. Images of historical documents and historic portraits are also included. The original order, accession numbers, and handwritten descriptions on the slides were maintained as close as possible while processing and indexing this collection.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Fairfax County (Va.). Office of Comprehensive Planning. Heritage Resources Branch; Historic sites - Virginia - Fairfax County
Container List
- Accotink School (interior), c. 1907, Accotink, VA, Undated; Accotink-School-B1
- Accotink School (interior), c. 1907, Accotink, VA, Undated; Accotink-School-B2
- Sadie the Cow c. 1924, Herndon, VA, Undated; Agriculture-B3
- Sadie the Cow c. 1924, Herndon, VA, Undated; Agriculture-B4
- Herndon Area Farms, Herndon, VA, 1985; Agriculture-B6
- Acres Available, Undated; Agriculture-B7
- Annandale Methodist Church and Cemetery, Annandale, VA, 1976 June; Annandale-B1
- Cannon - 1907 Backlick Road and Columbia Pike, Annandale, VA, 1976 June; Annandale-B2
- Cannon - 1907 Backlick Road and Columbia Pike, Annandale, VA, Undated; Annandale-B3
- Cannon - 1907 Backlick Road and Columbia Pike, Annandale, VA, 1976 June; Annandale-B4
- Cannon - 1907 Backlick Road and Columbia Pike, Annandale, VA, Undated; Annandale-B5
- Gas Station Fairfax [Kenny's Amoco at 10549 Lee Highway], Fairfax, VA, Undated; Art-Deco-B6
- Tastee Diner, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Art-Deco-B8
- Tastee Diner, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Art-Deco-B9
- Gas Station Detail Fairfax [Kenny's Amoco at 10549 Lee Highway], Fairfax, VA, Undated; Art-Deco-B10
- Gas Station Detail Fairfax [Kenny's Amoco at 10549 Lee Highway], Fairfax, VA, Undated; Art-Deco-B11
- Gas Station Detail Fairfax [Kenny's Amoco at 10549 Lee Highway], Fairfax, VA, Undated; Art-Deco-B12
- Willoughby Newton Boundry Stone, Centreville, VA, Undated; Artifacts-B1
- Willoughby Newton Boundry Stone, Centreville, VA, Undated; Artifacts-B2
- Willoughby Newton Boundry Stone, Centreville, VA, Undated; Artifacts-B3
- Willoughby Newton Boundry Stone, Centreville, VA, Undated; Artifacts-B4
- Willoughby Newton Boundry Stone, Centreville, VA, Undated; Artifacts-B5
- Last Page Of Letter From Bryan Fairfax To George Washington - 17 July 1774, Undated; Artifacts-B6
- Tobacco Marks, Undated; Artifacts-B8
- Tobacco Marks, Undated; Artifacts-B9
- Registration Of Free Negroes, Undated; Artifacts-B10
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B1
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B2
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B3
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B4
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B5
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B6
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B7
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B8
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B9
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B10
- Exterior of Ashland house, Alexandria, VA, 1988 October; Ashland-B11
- Ballantrae Sub-Division, McLean, VA, Undated; Ballantrae-B1
- Ballantrae Sub-Division, McLean, VA, Undated; Ballantrae-B2
- Barn- Herndon Area Middleton Farm, Herndon, VA, Undated; Barn-B2
- Barn- Herndon Area Middleton Farm, Herndon, VA, 1985 April; Barn-B4
- Barn at Level Green, Centreville, VA, Undated; Barn-B7
- Bienvenue, McLean, VA, 1967; Bienvenue-B1
- Bienvenue, McLean, VA, 1981; Bienvenue-B2
- Bienvenue, McLean, VA, 1981; Bienvenue-B3
- Bienvenue, McLean, VA, 1981; Bienvenue-B4
- Quarry on Route 29 Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B2
- Quarry on Route 29 Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B3
- Quarry on Route 29 Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B4
- Quarry on Route 29 Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B5
- Quarry on Route 29, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B6
- View West on Route 29, Centreville, VA, 1989 December; Bull-B7
- Approach To Bull Run, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B8
- Approach To Bull Run, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B9
- Approach To Bull Run, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B10
- Industry on Route 29 Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B11
- Industry on Route 29 Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B12
- Current Plant on Route 29 - View to East, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B13
- Industry on Route 29, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B14
- Near Bull Run HD, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B15
- Industry on Route 29, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B16
- Bull Run Grill on Route 29, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B17
- Parking Lot - Bull Run Grill on Route 29, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B18
- Route 29, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B19
- Route 29 - View West, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B20
- Route 29 - View East, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B21
- Route 29 Bull Run HD, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B22
- Park Sign - Manassas National Battlefield Park, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B23
- Route 29 Bull Run HD - Fairfax County Historical Marker, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B24
- Stone Bridge, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B25
- Route 29, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B26
- Bridge, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B27
- Bull Run Stone Bridge HD, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B28
- Bull Run, Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B29
- Park Sign Fairfax County. View West on Route 29 - Manassas National Battlefield Park, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B30
- Bull Run(HD), Centreville, VA, 1972 August; Bull-B31
- Bull Run(HD), Centreville, VA, 1989 December; Bull-B32
- Bull Rull Stone Bridge, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B34
- Bull Run Stone Bridge, Centreville, VA, Undated; Bull-B35
- Bull Run Stone Bridge, Centreville, VA, 1985 December; Bull-B37
- Mount Vernon Influence Near Burke, Burke, VA, 1979; Burke-B1
- Silas Burke House, Exterior View, Burke, VA, 1988 September; Burke-House-B1
- Silas Burke House, Exterior View, Burke, VA, 1988 September; Burke-House-B4
- Silas Burke House, Exterior View, Burke, VA, 1988 September; Burke-House-B6
- Silas Burke House, Exterior View, Burke, VA, 1988 September; Burke-House-B7
- Silas Burke House, Burke, VA, 1988 September; Burke-House-B8
- Silas Burke House, Burke, VA, 1988 September; Burke-House-B9
- Silas Burke House Area, Burke, VA, 1988 September; Burke-House-B10
- St. John's Church, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B4
- St. John's Church, Centreville, VA, 1989 December; Centreville-B5
- St. John's Church, Centreville, VA, 1989 February; Centreville-B6
- Old Stone Church, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B7
- Old Stone Church, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B8
- Old Stone Church (Centreville Methodist), Centreville, VA, 1984 November; Centreville-B9
- Mt. Gilead Rd. Leading To St. John's, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B10
- Mt. Gilead Rd. Looking Towards To St. John's, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B11
- Mt. Gilead Rd. Empty Lot, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B12
- Mt. Gilead Rd. Looking Northwest, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B13
- Mt. Gilead Rd. Entrance To Mt. Gilead (On Right), Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B14
- Mt. Gilead Rd. View From Edge of District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B15
- Mt.Gilead Rd. From Curve Looking Toward Braddock Road, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B16
- Braddock Road Looking Southeast, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B17
- Braddock Road, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B18
- Havener House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B20
- Havener House HD, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B21
- Havener House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B22
- Old Stone House behind Havener House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B23
- Harrison House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B24
- Harrison House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B25
- Sears House Lot 39, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B28
- Sears House Lot 39, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B29
- 5641 Mt. Gilead Rd., Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B30
- 5640 Mt. Gilead Rd., Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B31
- Mt. Gilead HD, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B32
- Mt. Gilead from Mt. Gilead Rd., Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B34
- Willoughby's Ridge Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B35
- Office Building Corner Of Mt. Gilead and Braddock Road, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B36
- Office Building and Harrison House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B37
- 13914 Braddock Road Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B38
- 13914 Braddock Road Rear View, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B39
- 13923 Braddock Rd. Near Historic District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B40
- Centreville Architecture, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B41
- Walney, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B42
- Willoughby Ridge Ln. Mt. Gilead- 1989, Centreville, VA, Centreville-B43
- Havener House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B46
- Mt. Gilead- 1967 E. Breitehbach, Centreville, VA, Centreville-B47
- Willoughby Ridge Ln. Mt. Gilead- 1989, Centreville, VA, Centreville-B48
- Harrison House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B49
- Centreville Architecture, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B50
- Centreville Road Farm- 1985, Centreville, VA, 1985 April; Centreville-B51
- Mt. Gilead- 1989 Carriage House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B52
- Mt. Gilead Carriage House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B52
- Mt. Gilead- 1989 Carriage House, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B54
- 19th century Church Route 28 at Old Centreville Road, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B55
- Civil War, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B56
- Civil War, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B57
- Harrison House, Centreville, VA, 1989 December; Centreville-B58
- Hopkins Map - Centreville District, Centreville, VA, Undated; Centreville-B59
- The 3rd Chain Bridge 1805, Undated; Chain-Bridge-B2
- Hermitage- Clifton, Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B1
- Hermitage- Clifton, Clifton, VA, 1980 January; Clifton-B3
- Chapel Street, March 1974, J.L. Fimglass, Clifton, VA, 1974 March; Clifton-B7
- Hetzel House Pendleton Ave. and Chapel Rd. March 1974, Clifton, VA, 1974 March; Clifton-B8
- Clifton, Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B9
- Clifton, Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B10
- Ford House, Ford Lane March 1974, J.L. Fimglass, Clifton, VA, 1974 March; Clifton-B11
- Quigg House Clifton, Clifton, VA, 1972 March; Clifton-B12
- Clifton- Main St., Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B13
- Clifton House, Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B15
- Clifton Main St., Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B16
- Clifton, Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B18
- Clifton, Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B19
- Hermitage- Clifton Main St., Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B20
- Hermitage- Clifton Main St., Clifton, VA, 1974 March; Clifton-B21
- Hermitage Clifton Hotel, Clifton, VA, Undated; Clifton-B22
- Hermitage Clifton Hotel, Clifton, VA, 1993 April 26; Clifton-B23
- Hermitage Clifton Hotel, Clifton, VA, 1993 April 26; Clifton-B24
- Colvin Run Mill- Oliver Evans, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B1
- Colvin Run Mill Dedication-1972, Great Falls, VA, 1972 July; CRM-B2
- Colvin Run Mill Dedication-1972, Great Falls, VA, CRM-B3
- Colvin Run Mill Interior, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B4
- Colvin Run Mill Works- c. 1974, Great Falls, VA, CRM-B5
- Colvin Run Mill Works- c. 1974, Great Falls, VA, CRM-B6
- Barn- Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1984; CRM-B7
- Colvin Run Mill Millers House, Great Falls, VA, 1972 November; CRM-B8
- Colvin Run Mill Millers House West-1974, Great Falls, VA, 1974 May; CRM-B9
- Country Store Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B10
- Country Store Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1979; CRM-B11
- Colvin Run Mill Historic Photo, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B12
- Colvin Run Mill Historic Photo, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B13
- Colvin Run Mill Old Photo, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B14
- Colvin Run Mill Historic Photo, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B15
- Colvin Run Mill Water Wheel, Great Falls, VA, 1974 May; CRM-B17
- Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1972 November; CRM-B18
- Miller's House At Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1980 January; CRM-B19
- Detail Of Break Repair On Miller House, Great Falls, VA, 1989 November; CRM-B20
- Colvin Run Mill District Fairfax County, Great Falls, VA, 1990 October; CRM-B21
- Colvin Run Community House, Great Falls, VA, 1989 March; CRM-B22
- Colvin Run Mill District Fairfax County, Great Falls, VA, 1990 October; CRM-B23
- General Store at Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1978 August; CRM-B24
- Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, 1984 September; CRM-B27
- Colvin Run Mill Sign, Great Falls, VA, 1987 September; CRM-B28
- Colvin Run Mill, Great Falls, VA, Undated; CRM-B29
- Leigh House-Colvin Run Rd., Great Falls, VA, 1989 March; CRM-B30
- Tricket's House Near Colvin Run, Great Falls, VA, 1972 November; CRM-B31
- Dranesville Tavern Historic Photo, Dranesville, VA, Undated; Dranesville-B1
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, Undated; Dranesville-B2
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, 1979; Dranesville-B3
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, 1976; Dranesville-B4
- Dranesville Tavern (From Rear), Dranesville, VA, 1978; Dranesville-B5
- Dranesville Tavern (Winter), Dranesville, VA, Undated; Dranesville-B6
- Dranesville Tavern 1968, Dranesville, VA, Dranesville-B8
- Dranesville Tavern 1968, Dranesville, VA, Dranesville-B9
- Dranesville Tavern 1968, Dranesville, VA, Dranesville-B10
- Dranesville Tavern 1968, Dranesville, VA, Dranesville-B11
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, Undated; Dranesville-B12
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, 1980 January; Dranesville-B13
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, 1972 November; Dranesville-B14
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, 1972 November; Dranesville-B15
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, 1971 November; Dranesville-B16
- Dranesville Tavern 1918, Dranesville, VA, Undated; Dranesville-B17
- Dranesville Tavern '68, Dranesville, VA, 1968; Dranesville-B18
- Dranesville Tavern, Dranesville, VA, 1976; Dranesville-B19
- Dulles International Airport, Dulles, VA, Undated; Dulles-B1
- Truro Parish House, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-City-B1
- Fairfax Herald, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-City-B2
- Fairfax Herald, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-City-B3
- Truro Episcopal Rectory- Fairfax City, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-City-B4
- Fairfax Herald Bulding, Fairfax, VA, 1984 September; Fairfax-City-B5
- Fairfax Court House, 1863, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-Co.-B4
- 1800 Fairfax Court House (3rd C.H.), Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-Co.-B5
- Restored Interior Courthouse, Fairfax, VA, 1980 January; Fairfax-Co.-B6
- Fairfax County Jail and Additions c.1885, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-Co.-B8
- Court House Marker Stone, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-Co.-B9
- Fairfax Courthouse c.1860, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-Co.-B10
- 1800 Fairfax Court House, Fairfax, VA, Undated; Fairfax-Co.-B12
- Fairfax Station, 1919, Fairfax Station, VA, Undated; Fairfax-Station-B3
- Gordon Road-Falls Church (Old Trolley Row), Falls Church, VA, Undated; Falls-Church-B2
- Gordon's Road-Falls Church Trolley Route (Row) ca. 1900, Falls Church, VA, Undated; Falls-Church-B3
- Floris, Floris, VA, 1985; Floris-B1
- Bowman's Store Floris, Floris, VA, 1991; Floris-B2
- Floris House, Floris, VA, 1985; Floris-B3
- Bowman's Store Floris, Floris, VA, Undated; Floris-B4
- Floris House- 1985, Floris, VA, 1985 April; Floris-B5
- Floris Area- 1985, Floris, VA, Floris-B6
- Floris- 1985, Floris, VA, 1985 April; Floris-B7
- Floris- 1985, Floris, VA, 1985 April; Floris-B8
- Floris- 1985, Floris, VA, Floris-B9
- Floris Methodist Church- 1985, Floris, VA, Floris-B10
- Bowman's Store near Frying Pan Park, Floris, VA, Undated; Floris-B11
- Floris Church, Floris, VA, 1985 April; Floris-B12
- Fort Belvior Fall 1985, Fort Belvoir, VA, 1985 Fall; Ft.-Belvior-B1
- Fort Belvior Fall 1985, Fort Belvoir, VA, 1985 Fall; Ft.-Belvior-B2
- Fort Lyon, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Ft.-Lyon-B1
- Fort Lyon, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Ft.-Lyon-B2
- Four Stairs, Great Falls, VA, 1989 March; Four-Stairs-B1
- Ruins of Middle Turnpike Bridge over Difficult Run, Great Falls, VA, 1978 August; Great-Falls-B1
- Great Falls, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Great-Falls-B2
- Great Falls Grange, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Great-Falls-B3
- Great Falls Grange, Great Falls, VA, Undated; Great-Falls-B4
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B1
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B2
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B3
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B4
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B5
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B6
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B7
- Green Spring Farm Exterior View, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B8
- Green Spring Farm Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B9
- Green Spring Farm Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B11
- Green Spring Farm Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B12
- Green Spring Farm Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B13
- Green Spring Farm Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B14
- Green Spring Farm Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B15
- Historic Photo- Mosby 3rd from left at Fairfax County Courthouse, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B16
- Green Spring Farm Historic Photo, Alexandria, VA, Undated; Green-Spring-B10
- Groveton house, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B1
- Groveton Park, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B2
- Stoneybrooke Park, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B3
- Groveton apartments, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B4
- Groveton houses, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B5
- Groveton house, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B6
- Groveton School, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B7
- Groveton, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B8
- Groveton houses, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B9
- Groveton, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B10
- Groveton church, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B11
- Groveton, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B12
- Groveton, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B13
- Groveton, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B14
- Groveton, Groveton, VA, Undated; Groveton-B15
- Presbyterian Church at Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 November; Gum-Spring-B12
- Presbyterian Church at Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 November; Gum-Spring-B13
- Presbyterian Church at Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 November; Gum-Spring-B14
- Baptist Church at Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 November; Gum-Spring-B15
- Baptist Church, Gum Springs, VA, Undated; Gum-Spring-B18
- Baptist Church at Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, Undated; Gum-Spring-B19
- Baptist Church at Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 November; Gum-Spring-B22
- Peake Family Cemetery, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 October; Gum-Spring-B23
- Peake Family Cemetery, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 October; Gum-Spring-B24
- Peake Family Cemetery, Gum Springs, VA, 1979 October; Gum-Spring-B25
- Fairfax County, Va Gum Springs Marker, Gum Springs, VA, 1991 November; Gum-Spring-B55
- Fairfax County, Va Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, 1991 November; Gum-Spring-B57
- Fairfax County, Va Gum Springs, Gum Springs, VA, 1991 November; Gum-Spring-B60
- Gum Springs 1940s, Gum Springs, VA, Undated; Gum-Spring-B61
- Gunston Hall Gardens, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B1
- Entrance From River, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B2
- Stairwell/Pillar and Arch Paper - Gunston Hall, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B4
- Stairwell/Pillar and Arch Paper, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B5
- Palladian Room Gunston Hall, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B6
- Formal Parlor (Pre-1986), Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B7
- Chinese-Style Dining Room, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B8
- Chippendale Dining Room, Gunston, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B12
- Parlor Door/ restored rosettes, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B13
- Aerial View, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B15
- Aerial View, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B16
- Aerial View of Gardens- Gunston Hall, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B17
- Gunston Hall, Lorton, VA, 1991 December; Gunston-B20
- Gunston Hall, Lorton, VA, 1991 December; Gunston-B21
- Gunston Hall Gardens, Lorton, VA, 1991 December; Gunston-B22
- Gunston Hall Gardens, Lorton, VA, 1991 December; Gunston-B23
- Gunston Hall Entrance, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B24
- Carriage Approach To Gunston Hall, Lorton, VA, 1984 September; Gunston-B28
- Gunston Hall Gardens, Lorton, VA, Undated; Gunston-B30